{
    "id": "27f4ab9fba2044ab8ab3e395318a8824",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She seems nice. ………………… .., I don’t really like her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Even so",
                "Even though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "49a615eb704e4686838ebb1ed0919be4"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. I become a millionaire, I will always be a socialist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Even if",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1f9ba64aeb6641f5920fa3872e2bcb19"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Are you interested in going to university?’ ‘Yes, I ………………’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would like",
                "would like to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cabe6a25ded24e528cd4fce256df0a7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I’ll try to phone you …………………… the meeting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a6dd447b9f0445358bc54736dd4d5bca"
        },
        {
            "question": "I woke up …………………… the night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "during",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eea239833ed34355b5a4d17119571647"
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t recognize him because he was dressed …………….. a dark suit.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6d7fc325a25840ec894f9b3a48aaccdb"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… the bad weather, the match was cancelled.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "Due to",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "09c9e16fc19b4cc4b37573331d0b1f44"
        },
        {
            "question": "I’ve been to ………………….. too many places recently.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "quite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7e0d5ff4ebd64f3a9d09278c0eb5e0b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a …………………. unpleasant experience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "rather"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "41533f54493b49eca8528c35767cbf72"
        },
        {
            "question": "He’s not ………………….. to be a soldier.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall enough",
                "enough tall"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b8fe0d9b4f424064b45bd5273dc5ec63"
        }
    ]
}